<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">MyApp</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="ada">Ada Lovelace</string>
    <string name="lovelace">Photo</string>
    <string name="biography1"> The daughter of famed poet Lord Byron, Augusta Ada Byron, Countess of Lovelace—better known 
        as "Ada Lovelace"—was born in London on December 10, 1815. Ada showed her gift for mathematics at an early age. 
        She translated an article on an invention by Charles Babbage, and added her own comments. Because she introduced 
        many computer concepts, Ada is considered the first computer programmer. Ada died on November 27,1852.
        More than a hundred years after her death, in 1953, Ada Lovelace\'s notes on Babbage\'s Analytical Engine were republished
         after having been forgotten. The engine was now recognized as a model for a computer, and Ada Lovelace\'s notes 
         as a description of a computer and software. In 1980, the U.S. Department of Defense settled on the name
         "Ada" for a new standardized computer language, named in honor of Ada Lovelace.</string>

    <string name="john">John von Neumann</string>
    <string name="neumann">Photo</string>
    <string name="biography2">Hungarian-born American mathematician. As an adult, he appended von to
         his surname; the hereditary title had been granted his father in 1913. Von Neumann grew from 
         child prodigy to one of the world\'s foremost mathematicians by his mid-twenties. Important work
          in set theory inaugurated a career that touched nearly every major branch of mathematics. Von 
          Neumann’s gift for applied mathematics took his work in directions that influenced quantum theory,
           automata theory, economics, and defense planning. Von Neumann pioneered game theory and, along 
           with Alan Turing and Claude Shannon, was one of the conceptual inventors of the stored-program 
           digital computer. Hungarian-born American mathematician. As an adult, he appended von to
         his surname; the hereditary title had been granted his father in 1913. Von Neumann grew from 
         child prodigy to one of the world\'s foremost mathematicians by his mid-twenties. Important work
          in set theory inaugurated a career that touched nearly every major branch of mathematics. Von 
          Neumann’s gift for applied mathematics took his work in directions that influenced quantum theory,
           automata theory, economics, and defense planning. Von Neumann pioneered game theory and, along 
           with Alan Turing and Claude Shannon, was one of the conceptual inventors of the stored-program 
           digital computer.</string>
</resources>
